cellularfactory.com 2008-12-16

# CellularFactory.com Customer Service Center

**CELLULARFACTORY PRIVACY POLICY**

Echen Inc. is the single owner and doing business at CellularFactory.com.   
**Last Updated on 11/23/2007**

This privacy statement covers the site www.cellularfactory.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.   
1\. What personally identifiable information CellularFactory collects.   
2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.   
3\. What organization collects the information.   
4\. How CellularFactory uses the information.   
5\. With whom CellularFactory may share user information.   
6\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.   
7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under CellularFactory control.   
8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact our Customer Service Department by sales@cellularfactory.com, 1-626-855-4620, 1750 Old Canyon Drive, Hacienda Heights, CA 91745. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection**   
CellularFactory is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. CellularFactory collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**Registration**   
During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Order**   
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. 

**Information Use**   
The information you provide us will only be used for processing orders and informing our customers of upcoming promotions or newsletters. 

**Profile**   
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

We use cookies to personalize the site for your ease of use. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes, contests or monthly drawings that take place. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by CellularFactory only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Log Files**   
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Communications from the Site**   
**Special Offers and Updates**   
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. To opt-out please click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any transmissions. 

**Customer Service**   
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**   
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Third Party Advertisers**   
We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties. 

**Third Party Intermediaries**   
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Our payment processing partners include, Card Services International, Paypal and Google Checkout. 

**Business Transitions**   
In the event CellularFactory goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Choice/Opt-out**   
Our users are given the opportunity to ~Qopt-out~R of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ~Qopt-out~R mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don~Rt want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.   
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at sales@cellularfactory.com.   
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

**Links**   
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Echen Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. [Discuss co-branding and/or framing relations where the user may not know who is collecting the information]. 

**Surveys & Contests**   
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users~R personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users~R personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. CellularFactory will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. CellularFactory does not store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact CellularFactory. at http://www.cellularfactory.com/help/contact_us.jsp to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Security**   
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users~R information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.   
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just surfing. To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://www. verisign.com.   
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users~R information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every [quarter], as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users~R information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility.   
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to sales@cellularfactory.com. 

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

**Correcting / Updating / Deleting / Deactivating Personal Information**   
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the [member information page] or by emailing our Customer Support at sales@cellularfactory.com. Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.   
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email, and by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

**Contact Information**   
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

Phone : 1-626-855-4620   
Fax : 1-626-855-4621   
Email : sales@cellularfactory.com   
Postal Address   
1750 Old Canyon Dr. Hacienda Heights, CA 91745   
Web site URL https://www.cellularfactory.com 

       Contact: 

cellularfactory.com  
1750 Old Canyon Dr. Hacienda Heights, CA 91745  
Tel: (888)952-6550  
Tel: 1-626-855-4620  
Fax: 1-626-855-4621 

**FREE Cell Phone Website for Your Business**  
Profit from your own cell phone website. We already have many partners generating several thousand dollars monthly.  
[Click here](http://www.cellularfactory.com/affiliate/new_member.jsp) for details.

 Customer Service (888)952-6550  
8am-5pm PST M-F |    
---|---
